Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 5 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Notice Period: 2 Months

Charulata Khotele 🕡 Featured

Software Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, PHP, Python, MySQL, MS SQL Server, T-SQL, PL/SQL, JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, GIT, JIRA



Current Designation: Software Engineer -Software

Development

Current Company: SEARCE

Current Location: Pune

Pref. Location: Nagpur, Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, PHP, Python, MySQL, MS SQL Server, T-

SQL,PL/SQL,JavaScript,JQuery,HTML,CSS,GIT,JIRA

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

Result-oriented Professional with over 3 years of experience in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution Architecture, PHP, Python, MySQL, MS SQL Server, T-SQL, PL/SQL, JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, GIT, JIRA.

Work Experience

SEARCE as Software Engineer -Software Development Jul 2019 to Till Date

RESPONSIBILITIES

SQL development like Stored Procedure, SQL Queries, Functions, Index, etc.

2 year hand on experience in core PHP, PHP MVC

Develop record and maintain cutting edge web based PHP application.

Development of internal Portals using PHP, AJAX, MYSQL, CSS,JS.

Good with unit testing, also familiar with JIRA, GitHub.

Work with Team in an agile, also open for new technology changes and challenges.

Krish InfoTech, Nagpur as PHP Developer - Software developer Apr 2018 to Apr 2019

Alive Tech, Nagpur as Trainee Oct 2017 to Apr 2019

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Kavikulguru Institute of Technology and Science in 2016

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
PHP			
Python			
MySQL			
MS SQL SERVER			
T-SQL, PL/SQL			
JavaScript			
JQuery, HTML, CSS			
git, Jira			
WINDOWS, LINUX			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time